[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "How are you coping since I last spoke to you as a family?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "coping", "since", "I", "last", "spoke", "to", "you", "as", "a", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "Well I'm doing the same things that we talked about in that interview.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "I", "'m", "doing", "the", "same", "things", "that", "we", "talked", "about", "in", "that", "interview", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "RB", ",", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "Bonnie what's your question for Rick Warren?", "question_tokens": ["Bonnie", "what", "'s", "your", "question", "for", "Rick", "Warren", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WP", "POS", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "I had a child that passed away and it's been 36 years and I've accepted it as much as I can and I'm living a normal life now but my struggle is trying to again, get peace with myself for why.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "a", "child", "that", "passed", "away", "and", "it", "'s", "been", "36", "years", "and", "I", "'ve", "accepted", "it", "as", "much", "as", "I", "can", "and", "I", "'m", "living", "a", "normal", "life", "now", "but", "my", "struggle", "is", "trying", "to", "again", ",", "get", "peace", "with", "myself", "for", "why", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Warren"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 26, "question": "Rick I suppose the general question on the back of that is, how can a loving God put people through such terrible pain of taking a child away?", "question_tokens": ["Rick", "I", "suppose", "the", "general", "question", "on", "the", "back", "of", "that", "is", ",", "how", "can", "a", "loving", "God", "put", "people", "through", "such", "terrible", "pain", "of", "taking", "a", "child", "away", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", ",", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "Yeah, well again as I said, it would be very easy for God to remove all the evil in the world, just take away my freedom to do it and your freedom to do it.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "well", "again", "as", "I", "said", ",", "it", "would", "be", "very", "easy", "for", "God", "to", "remove", "all", "the", "evil", "in", "the", "world", ",", "just", "take", "away", "my", "freedom", "to", "do", "it", "and", "your", "freedom", "to", "do", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "When did he finally get this gun?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "he", "finally", "get", "this", "gun", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "A month before he took his life.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "month", "before", "he", "took", "his", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "Who he got it from?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "he", "got", "it", "from", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "He told me that he -- he told me everything and he told me that he had found somebody finally on the internet who would sell it to him and it had to be super encrypted and it had to be, you know, this whole process and he begged me to help him because he couldn't figure out the process and again there's so many moments of terrible choices with mental illness.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "told", "me", "that", "he", "--", "he", "told", "me", "everything", "and", "he", "told", "me", "that", "he", "had", "found", "somebody", "finally", "on", "the", "internet", "who", "would", "sell", "it", "to", "him", "and", "it", "had", "to", "be", "super", "encrypted", "and", "it", "had", "to", "be", ",", "you", "know", ",", "this", "whole", "process", "and", "he", "begged", "me", "to", "help", "him", "because", "he", "could", "n't", "figure", "out", "the", "process", "and", "again", "there", "'s", "so", "many", "moments", "of", "terrible", "choices", "with", "mental", "illness", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "No one seems to be tackling this, what is the answer, how do we get to grips with this?", "question_tokens": ["No", "one", "seems", "to", "be", "tackling", "this", ",", "what", "is", "the", "answer", ",", "how", "do", "we", "get", "to", "grips", "with", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "I think one of the reasons why it's being hard to tackle is because there are so many guns out there.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "one", "of", "the", "reasons", "why", "it", "'s", "being", "hard", "to", "tackle", "is", "because", "there", "are", "so", "many", "guns", "out", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "What does that tell you about the state of the debate about it, before anything else?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "that", "tell", "you", "about", "the", "state", "of", "the", "debate", "about", "it", ",", "before", "anything", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "I don't know how they're going to attack it politically.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "how", "they", "'re", "going", "to", "attack", "it", "politically", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "And how do we tackle it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "do", "we", "tackle", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "Well I think you hit it on the head Piers when you said that the internet has really made a megaphone.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "I", "think", "you", "hit", "it", "on", "the", "head", "Piers", "when", "you", "said", "that", "the", "internet", "has", "really", "made", "a", "megaphone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "And you've actually -- you've had this?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "'ve", "actually", "--", "you", "'ve", "had", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Oh of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Monday", "Monday"]}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "CD", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "600?", "question_tokens": ["600", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "On Monday they closed down 13 just on Monday.", "answer_tokens": ["On", "Monday", "they", "closed", "down", "13", "just", "on", "Monday", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "JJ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "Now it probably is pure political as well as everything else but in the end, isn't it the Pope just effectively standing up as he always has done for the poor about what he said?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "it", "probably", "is", "pure", "political", "as", "well", "as", "everything", "else", "but", "in", "the", "end", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "the", "Pope", "just", "effectively", "standing", "up", "as", "he", "always", "has", "done", "for", "the", "poor", "about", "what", "he", "said", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Well absolutely, first he just have the authority of speaking as a man who spent his life helping the poor.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "absolutely", ",", "first", "he", "just", "have", "the", "authority", "of", "speaking", "as", "a", "man", "who", "spent", "his", "life", "helping", "the", "poor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "WP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "RB", "CC", "WP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "Are you recognizing that there is this seemingly unstoppable movement?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "recognizing", "that", "there", "is", "this", "seemingly", "unstoppable", "movement", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "Well, I don't get to change what God says is right and what God says is wrong.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "get", "to", "change", "what", "God", "says", "is", "right", "and", "what", "God", "says", "is", "wrong", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "RB", "DT", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Well, that term is from the Bible Right?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "term", "is", "from", "the", "Bible", "Right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "Well, I -- certainly the Bible -- it says God created marriage.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "--", "certainly", "the", "Bible", "--", "it", "says", "God", "created", "marriage", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "How are you going to get me healthier in 40 days?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "going", "to", "get", "me", "healthier", "in", "40", "days", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "Most diet plans are pretty simplistic 'cause they only deal with food and fitness.", "answer_tokens": ["Most", "diet", "plans", "are", "pretty", "simplistic", "'cause", "they", "only", "deal", "with", "food", "and", "fitness", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", ":", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "... so that's impressive doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["...", "so", "that", "'s", "impressive", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "This one is actually on physical health and -- and actually the reason why is that I discovered that a lot people want to change, make changes in their life but they don't have the energy to make changes.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "one", "is", "actually", "on", "physical", "health", "and", "--", "and", "actually", "the", "reason", "why", "is", "that", "I", "discovered", "that", "a", "lot", "people", "want", "to", "change", ",", "make", "changes", "in", "their", "life", "but", "they", "do", "n't", "have", "the", "energy", "to", "make", "changes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "Why should spirituality, the power of prayer, any of that stuff have any effect of my ability to be fit or lose weight?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "should", "spirituality", ",", "the", "power", "of", "prayer", ",", "any", "of", "that", "stuff", "have", "any", "effect", "of", "my", "ability", "to", "be", "fit", "or", "lose", "weight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "You know what's extraordinary Piers is that people change together in community.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", "'s", "extraordinary", "Piers", "is", "that", "people", "change", "together", "in", "community", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "How are you going to convince people in their heads, never mind anything else, to come and do this because if this is the master plan you got to persuade them?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "going", "to", "convince", "people", "in", "their", "heads", ",", "never", "mind", "anything", "else", ",", "to", "come", "and", "do", "this", "because", "if", "this", "is", "the", "master", "plan", "you", "got", "to", "persuade", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VB", "NN", "RB", ",", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "IN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "So there are a 140 studies now, that say as your weight goes up, the actual physical size, and function of your brain goes down.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "there", "are", "a", "140", "studies", "now", ",", "that", "say", "as", "your", "weight", "goes", "up", ",", "the", "actual", "physical", "size", ",", "and", "function", "of", "your", "brain", "goes", "down", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "That's true.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "When the brain smaller as you get fatter?", "question_tokens": ["When", "the", "brain", "smaller", "as", "you", "get", "fatter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack Daniels"]}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "The person with the good brain or the person with the bad brain?", "question_tokens": ["The", "person", "with", "the", "good", "brain", "or", "the", "person", "with", "the", "bad", "brain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "The person with the good bottle of Jack Daniels.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "person", "with", "the", "good", "bottle", "of", "Jack", "Daniels", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 363, "question": "Does it matter?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "matter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "So start reading the labels so get on the internet--", "answer_tokens": ["So", "start", "reading", "the", "labels", "so", "get", "on", "the", "internet", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "So tell me what are you hoping, well these audience said, many of them have tried and failed with diets through their lives what is the key take away here from this book that can change things?", "question_tokens": ["So", "tell", "me", "what", "are", "you", "hoping", ",", "well", "these", "audience", "said", ",", "many", "of", "them", "have", "tried", "and", "failed", "with", "diets", "through", "their", "lives", "what", "is", "the", "key", "take", "away", "here", "from", "this", "book", "that", "can", "change", "things", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "I mean it's very simple.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "it", "'s", "very", "simple", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 375, "question": "Plant food?", "question_tokens": ["Plant", "food", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Yeah, plant food, nuts, seeds, beans, whole of grains--", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "plant", "food", ",", "nuts", ",", "seeds", ",", "beans", ",", "whole", "of", "grains", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Can you eat as much wings as you like?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "eat", "as", "much", "wings", "as", "you", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "Me chicken, fish, all of those things are foods.", "answer_tokens": ["Me", "chicken", ",", "fish", ",", "all", "of", "those", "things", "are", "foods", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["MSG"]}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "PRP$", ",", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "NN", "NNS", ",", ":", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 383, "question": "What are the biggest no no's?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "biggest", "no", "no", "'s", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "DT", "DT", "POS", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "Sugar, flour, processed foods, factory foods,(inaudible), corn syrup, trans fats, MSG all these things that are -- the abundant things in our diet that are driving addiction--", "answer_tokens": ["Sugar", ",", "flour", ",", "processed", "foods", ",", "factory", "foods", ",", "(", "inaudible", ")", ",", "corn", "syrup", ",", "trans", "fats", ",", "MSG", "all", "these", "things", "that", "are", "--", "the", "abundant", "things", "in", "our", "diet", "that", "are", "driving", "addiction", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "What do you think has been the most effective thing for you in terms of loosing weight?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "has", "been", "the", "most", "effective", "thing", "for", "you", "in", "terms", "of", "loosing", "weight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Well there are three things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "there", "are", "three", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Christmas"], "LOCATION": ["Christmas"]}, "docId": "131206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "And Rick just a final question for you, obviously you said, the most difficult year of your life, how will you be spending Christmas this year as a family?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Rick", "just", "a", "final", "question", "for", "you", ",", "obviously", "you", "said", ",", "the", "most", "difficult", "year", "of", "your", "life", ",", "how", "will", "you", "be", "spending", "Christmas", "this", "year", "as", "a", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "You know, Christmas, there's three purposes of Christmas.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "Christmas", ",", "there", "'s", "three", "purposes", "of", "Christmas", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick"]}}]